

# RAJESH KUMAR Software Developer

Bangalore

☑ rajeshkr908070@gmail.com

**&** 8235571164

#### SOCIAL

@github

in @linkedin

@stackoverflow

#### PROFILE

Software Developer with 2+ years of experience in various technical fields like ReactJs, Angular, JavaScript, Java, NodeJs.I have work experience in domains like Retail, Banking and Insurance, delivered projects with tight deadlines in agile way.

#### EDUCATION

■ BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

KLS Gogte Institute Of Technology

2015 - 2019

**®** 9.5CGPA

SCIENCE - CBSE 12th Board

**DAV Public School** 

2013 - 2014

Grade A

CBSE 10th Board

**DAV Public School** 

2011 - 2012

**®** 9.8CGPA

#### SKILLS

- JavaScript
- React
- Html
- Angular
- CSS
- NodeJs
- Java

#### EXPERIENCE

#### SYSTEM ENGINEER | DEVELOPER

From Jul 2019 to present | Tata Consultancy Services Software Development with 2+ years of experience (React,Angular,Java,NodeJs).

#### SDE PROJECT INTERN

From Jan 2019 to May 2019 | Capillary Technologies
Web Development Intern (Angular, Java, Dockernetes, Kubernetes).

#### TELECOM NETWORKING PROJECT INTERN

From May 2017 to Jul 2017 | BSNL

Networking and Tele-Communication.

#### CERTIFICATES

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals (2021)

Microsoft Azure Certification, See credential

## Business English preliminary - University of Cambridge (2019)

Certified by Cambridge University for Business English.Certificate No.:0054504784

#### Udemy React and Java Certification (2021)

Certified by Udemy for course completion

### Udemy Angular Certification (2021)

Certified by Udemy for course completion

#### World Intellectual Property Organization - WIPO(2019)

WIPO Intellectual Property Rights Certication. Credential ID FtiUCWNImJ

#### ORGANIZATIONS

Associate Member

## Rotaract Club of GIT(Rotary Club)

Aug 2015 - Jul 2017
As an associate member of KLS GIT,
BELGAUM, chapter of ROTARACT CLUB OF
GIT, Involved in Traffic awareness and
Road safety projects/campaigns,
promoting and advertising students
friendly GK App(oust app) for children in
schools around Belgaum.

#### LANGUAGES

• English(Professional Working Proficiency) • Hindi(Native or Bilingual Proficiency)

#### INTEREST

>		7	Ф	4HÞ
Coding	Technology	Travel	Teaching	Fitness